I don't know what it means.
As expected.
The original is still a crafe.
I guess I don't know what's in it.
Like classical music,
What's that?
Yodeling.
Yodeling?
I enjoy listening to all kinds of genres,
I see.
I can go with just white rice. No side dish.
That's amazing.
I'm quite attracted to all-you-can-eat places.
I see.
I like that.
I like it.
Kettle and Idol
Well, here I am again today, the kettle kettle, the kenshi-shi raised kettle of Stardust.
Today we have a wonderful guest. This is my idol.
This is Aira from Ame-Karera. Please give her my best regards.
I'm Aira, from Ame no Karera.
Aira-san is here.
Yes, I'm Aira.
I have seen your work in various places,
Are you doing any commercials right now?
I'm currently working on a stage beauty study, a wu han beauty white sword, and so on,
I'm also working for Jiun Invoice,
Yes, that's right. That's right.
Eita's commercials are still running, aren't they?
That's right. Cabs and so on.
That's right.
I'm very grateful to have been allowed to do this.
I've been working on all fronts.
Yay!
Do you understand? I'm saying "Yay!
Eight-faceted and six-armed.
I don't understand. I don't know what it means.
You are the artist, aren't you? It means that you have many facets.
There is a word for that, too.
It's a good study.
Thank you very much. You are still a boy at heart.
A bit on the inside.
I didn't say that.
No, not at all.
Yes, I did.
Ira, you just finished the spring tour with AmeFlash.
That's right. It's over.
Thank you very much for your hard work.
Thank you very much.
It was a fun tour, that's the basic premise, but I think it was also a tour where we found a new way to showcase Ameflash,
But it was also a tour where we found a new way to showcase AmeFlash,
What exactly do you mean by that?
We are AmeFlash because our music is cool,
It's cool, isn't it?
We are very grateful for that,
We have a lot of songs that get the crowd going,
We don't have a lot of exciting songs,
But we broke up the dancing part of the show,
We also break up the usual dancing and get closer to the audience,
And we even play rock-paper-scissors during the songs,
Rock-paper-scissors during songs?
Yes, that's right. Because we were having an affair,
Even if you are yelling "yay" all the time,
Well, yes. That's the point.
So, if we were free, we would play rock-paper-scissors-scissors,
Or eating bananas during a song,
Bananas during a song?
My image has changed recently.
I was able to find a way to show that kind of gap,
I think it was a great tour.
I see.
But I also noticed that there are more and more women in the audience,
It's really starting to fill up,
The women's area is getting really panned, and so on,
The other day, we had Lily B. do the same thing,
The other day, we had Lily B, but we couldn't accommodate all the women.
We had Lily B the other day, but we couldn't fit enough women in there.
In the women's area.
Wow!
Aren't you so happy?
I'm so happy.
In the past, it was better if there was only one woman in AmeFresh.
So I'm really happy.
Men are happy, too,
As I said, at first it was just one person,
But now there are so many that we can't even get into the area,
I am really happy.
It is good to know that we are loved by everyone.
I am very grateful.
And from the festival held at the end of March,
I am very happy to hear everyone's voice at last.
I could finally hear everyone's voices,
I sang the first song,
From there, they started to get excited about Ayler, Amefresh, and Funew.
Yes, just like that?
Yes, like that,
I was so moved that I almost cried,
I was really moved, and I thought that everyone's voice was a great source of power.
Even if we didn't have to shout, we could all enjoy it together,
I was able to receive power from everyone,
But when I heard your voice, it was totally different.
Was it different?
It was totally different.
You and I...
Forever partners.
Night Tidings
I never put onions in.
I hate it when I cut them.
This show is...
Mr. Mackie
Aki Sada
Mikan Arai
Mr. Yoshiyuki
This program was provided by Mr. Tamagokakkakari
Thank you very much.